Finding Aid for the Augustus F. Hawkins papers LSC.1642
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Legislative Files, 1963-1990; (Contained in 39 Boxes)
  - 93rd Congress (), 1973-74
    - Bills Cosponsored
      - H.R. 15055, Railroads Not to Discriminate Against Movement of Non-Railroad Cars. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 17157, Reconstruction Finance Corp. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4792, Rent Control Board. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 12990, Restore Food Stamp Value. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10007, Restrict the Authority of Inspection of Income Tax Returns. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10181, Right to Financial Privacy Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 526, H.R. 9042, Runaway Youth Act of (2)., 1973 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 2650, Safe Schools Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.Res. 486, Salute to Hank Aaron. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4569, San Joaquin Wilderness. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8483, School Bus Safety Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.Res. 466, Select Committee to Investigate Energy Crisis Effects on the Poor. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10271, Senate Confirmation of Director and Deputy Director of Management and Budget. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 9380, Senior Citizens Transportation Act of, 1973. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7119, H.R. 9845, Sequoia National Park of the State of California (2). (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8314, Service, Employment, and Redevelopment (SER) Assistance Act. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 8316, H.R. 13023, Small Business Act, Amended (2). (Box 3)
      - Social Security Act Amendments
        - H.R. 4242, Extend for 5 Year Period. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 8018, Social Security Act Amended. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 16561, Nonprofit Retirement Home. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 15156, Cost of Living Increases. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 9955, Disability Insurance Benefits. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 12777, Include Breast Prosthesis. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 5612, Catastrophic Illness Insurance. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 7097, Medical Drugs and Prescriptions for Deductions. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 7498, Elective Coverage for Ministers as Employees. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 9903, Labor Strikes and Disputes. (Box 3)
        - H.J.Res. 433, H.R. 11169, H.R. 5627, Social Service Programs. (Box 3)
        - H.R. 12950, Increase Monthly Insurance Benefits. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4419, Social Security Benefit Increases. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4563, Social Security Disability Insurance Benefits. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 11005, Immediate 7% Increase Effective, January 1974. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 4887, Increase in Benefits., 1972 (Box 3)
      - H.R. 10584, Social Security Increase in Benefits for Guam and the Virgin Islands. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7092, Social Security, Outside Income for the Elderly. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 7091, Social Security, Payment Under Supplementary Medical Insurance. (Box 3)
      - H.R. 12947, Social Security Taxes Reduction. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 268, South African Enterprises of U.S. Firms. (Box 3)
      - H.J.Res. 785, Special Prosecution Conservancy Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.Con.Res. 466, Statue or Bust of Martin Luther King, Jr. for Capitol. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 14011, Study Feasibility of National Park for San Francisco Bay Area. (Box 4)
      - H.Res. 1067, Salute to Hank Aaron. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 15165, Sugar Act of, Amended., 1948 (Box 4)
      - H.R. 13538, Tariff Act of, Amended., 1930 (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8496, Task Force Within VA to Coordinate Programs for Vietnam Era Veterans. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 716, Tax Benefits for Unmarried (Full Benefits). (Box 4)
      - H.R. 4994, Tax Exempt Organizations for Lobbying. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 1041, Tax Equity Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8715, Telephone Privacy Act. (Box 4)
      - H.Res. 1157, Televising of Impeachment Debates of President of U.S. in House. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 16422, Terminate Age Discrimination in Employment. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 6650, Theft Losses Deduction in Computing Taxes. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 3905, Transportation Improvements to Avoid Air Pollution. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 3701, H.R. 11920, Truth in Food Labeling Act (2). (Box 4)
      - H.J.Res. 507, Tule Elk National Wildlife Refuge. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 13871, U.S. Code, Amended, Compensation for Work Injuries. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 13985, H.R. 14779, United States Housing Act of (2)., 1937 (Box 4)
      - H.R. 5869, H.R. 6606, USS Arizona Memorial. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 15870, Unrestricted Service Pension for World War I Veterans and Their Widows. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 4856, H.R. 4064, Urban Recreational Opportunities Act of (2)., 1973 (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8800, Veterans Educational Assistance. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8799, Veterans Emergency Hospital Treatment. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 13401, Veterans Pension and Compensation. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 10882, Vietnam Era Veterans Readjustment Assistance Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 6793, Vietnamese Orphans. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 2250, H.R. 9058, Vocational Rehabilitation Act, Amended (2). (Box 4)
      - H.R. 5852, Weather Modification Regulations Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 10155, West Coast Corridor Feasibility Study Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.Con.Res. 220, Withdrawal of U.S. Troops from Europe. (Box 4)
      - H.Con.Res. 578, Withdrawal of Foreign Troops from Cyprus. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 10133, Women's Educational Equity Act of, 1973. (Box 4)
      - H.Res. 1240, World Food Crisis Bill. (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8270, H.R. 16420, Youth Camp Safety Act (2). (Box 4)
      - H.R. 8433, H.R. 14897, Youth Conservation Corps Act of, Amended (2)., 1972 (Box 4)
    - Committee Files
      - Appropriations Committee. (Box 4)
      - Armed Services Committee. (Box 4)
      - Banking and Currency Committee. (Box 4)
      - Budget Committee. (Box 4)
      - Commerce Committee. (Box 4)
      - Committee on Committees. (Box 4)
      - District of Columbia Committee. (Box 4)
      - Foreign Affairs Committee. (Box 4)
      - Government Operations Committee. (Box 4)
      - House Administration Committee. (Box 4)
      - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee. (Box 4)
      - Internal Security Committee. (Box 4)
      - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee (2). (Box 5)
      - Joint Atomic Energy Committee. (Box 5)
      - Judiciary Committee. (Box 5)
      - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee. (Box 5)
      - Post Office and Civil Service Committee. (Box 5)
      - Public Works Committee. (Box 5)
      - Rules Committee. (Box 5)
      - Veterans' Affairs Committee. (Box 5)
      - Ways and Means Committee (2). (Box 5)
      - Miscellaneous (2). (Box 5)
    - Education and Labor Committee Files
      - Education and Labor Committee. (Box 5)
      - Education and Labor Committee (3). (Box 6)
      - Education and Labor Members. (Box 6)
      - Economic Opportunity Act Hearings. (Box 6)
      - SubCommittee on Equal Opportunities. (Box 6)
      - Public Law 93-355, Legal Services Corp. Act. (Box 6)
    - Brownsville Legislation, 1973
      - Research Material. (Box 6)
      - H.R. 6866. (Box 6)
      - H.R. 4382. (Box 6)
      - Senate Bills and Reports. (Box 6)
      - Public Law 93-177, Section 7. (Box 6)
      - Draft Bill Copies. (Box 6)
      - Congressional Correspondence. (Box 6)
      - Correspondence with U.S. Army. (Box 6)
      - Letters to Widows re Public Law. (Box 6)
      - Correspondence with John Weaver. (Box 6)
      - Mailing List and Correspondence with News Media. (Box 6)
      - Press Release
        - October 18, 1972. (Box 6)
        - November 30, 1972. (Box 6)
        - February 20, 1973. (Box 6)
        - June 5, 1973. (Box 6)
        - June 11, 1973. (Box 6)
        - November 16, 1973. (Box 6)
      - General Correspondence. (Box 6)
      - Miscellaneous Material. (Box 7)
      - Correspondence with Possible Recipients of Benefits. (Box 7)
      - List of Widows. (Box 7)
      - Congressional Record Inserts, March 7, 1973. (Box 7)
      - Congressional Record Inserts, March 18, 1973. (Box 7)
      - News Clippings. (Box 7)
      - Member's Hearing Statements. (Box 7)
      - List of Soldiers and Addresses. (Box 7)
      - Brownsville Memos from Higgs. (Box 7)
      - Veterans Administration Correspondence and Information from Archives Research. (Box 7)
  - 94th Congress (), 1975-76
    - Congressional Record Index (Showing Mr. Hawkins, Bills) List of Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored Bills Sponsored
      - H.R. 6648, For Relief of Danelia Alvarez de Bell. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 6647, For Relief of Guillermo Bell. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2208, Civil Rights Enforcement Office Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2207, Community Land Grant Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8578, Community Services Act of, Amended, re Federal Financial Assistance., 1974 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8991, Community Services Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 12188, Community Services Act Technical Amendments of, 1976. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 12216, Domestic Volunteer Services Act, Amended. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8622, Economic Rights of Labor in Building and Construction Industry. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 3240, Education Equalization Incentive Grants to the States. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7773, H.R. 1609, H.R. 2209, H.R. 7533, H.R. 50, H.R. 11589, H.R. 14036, Equal Opportunity and Full Employment Act (7). (Box 7)
      - H.R. 12001, Internal Revenue Code of, Amended., 1954 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8872, Internal Revenue Code of, Amended, re Disability Pension., 1954 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8874, Internal Revenue Code, Amended, re Public Retirement System. (Box 7)
      - H.Res. 1044, LEAA Budget Authority. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2276, Legal Practice Equal Opportunity Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 15904, H.R. 2206, H.R. 5937, Mexican-American Rural Community Anti-Poverty Act of (3)., 1975 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2205, Public Service Employment Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8873, Social Security Act, Amended, re Lump-Sum Death Payments. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7573, For the Relief of Ethline McRae Thomas. (Box 7)
      - H.Con.Res. 708, Volunteer Work To Be Taken Into Account by Public and Private Employers for Employment Purposes. (Box 7)
    - Congressional Record Index (Showing Mr. Hawkins, Bills) List of Bills Sponsored and Cosponsored Bills Coponsored
      - H.R. 4134, Abolish the Death Penalty. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 5718, Academies Admission Without Discrimination. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10400, Adoption by Executive Branch, Rules and Regulations. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 1659, Advertising of Alcoholic Beverages to not be Deductible Expenses. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 11678, Aerosol Ingredient Disclosure Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 11974, Agency to Administer the Internal Revenue Laws. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2038, Airport Noise Curfew Act. (Box 7)
      - H.J.Res. 433, Amend Constitution to Provide Representation in Congress for D.C. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 13600, Amend Title 38, U.S. Code, re Authorization of Expenditures for Veterans Dwellings. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 48, H.R. 17443, Animal Food Products, Foreign and Domestic Food Relief Programs (2). (Box 7)
      - H.Con.Res. 138, Appreciation to Mr. Frank Wills H.Res. 1521, Approval for Certain Travel by Committee. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7782, Arts, Humanities, and Cultural Affairs Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 12838, Arts, Humanities, and Cultural Affairs Act of, 1976. (Box 7)
      - H.J.Res. 608, Atlantic Convention. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7433, Autistic Children Research Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 13522, Authorization to Establish and Operate a National Museum of Afro-American History. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10425, Bill of Rights Procedures Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8201, Bureaucratic Accountability Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7386, Campuses for the Elderly Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 4352, Child Care Centers, Status as Educational Institutions. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2966, Child and Family Services Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 4624, Civil Rights Act of, Amended, re Discrimination Against Disabled Persons., 1964 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8742, Civil Rights Act of, Amended, re Attorney Fees., 1964 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 13928, Civil Rights Amendments of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10669, Roberto Clemente Sports City Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 1676, H.R. 17633, Coastal Zone Management Act of, Amended (2)., 1972 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 13435, Commission on Organization of Executive Branch of the Government. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 12316, Community-Based Day Treatment and In-Home Services for Children. (Box 7)
      - H.Res. 593, Commission to Study Circumstances Surrounding Deaths of Kennedys, Martin Luther King, and Attempted Assassination of George Wallace. (Box 7)
      - H.R, 8933, Commodity Credit Corporation Charter Act, Amended. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 4349, Comprehensive Child Development Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 3407, Comprehensive Employment and Training Act of, Amended., 1973 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8887, H.R. 10888, Comprehensive National Health Care Act of (2)., 1975 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 13021, Comprehensive Youth Employment Act of, 1976. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 5524, Concentrated Industries Anti-Inflation Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2583, Congressional Approval of Tariffs on Petroleum Imports. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 9100, Congressional Public Financing Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 8712, Conservation and Solar Energy, Federal Buildings Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 4562, Corporate Facility and Job Relocation Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 11110, Corporate Management Interlocks Act. (Box 7)
      - H.Res. 1313, Create a Select Committee on the Fiscal Problems of Cities. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10601, Create Young Adult Conservation Corps. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 14785, D-Q University. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 4507, Direct Low-Interest Loan Program Under Department of Housing and Urban Development. (Box 7)
      - H.Res. 681, Disapproving of Efforts to Expel Israel from the United Nations. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10736, Domestic Volunteer Service Act of, Amended., 1973 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 5126, Double-Pricing in Supermarkets. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7217, Education for All Handicapped Children Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7217, Education for All Handicapped Children Act of, Amended., 1975 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 5610, Education Amendments of, Amended., 1974 (Box 7)
      - H.R. 11137, Dwight D. Eisenhower Memorial Bicentennial Civic Center Act, Amended. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7382, Elderly Day Care Center Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 2035, Elderly and Handicapped Americans Transportation Services Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 7654, Electric Utilities Rate Reform Act of, 1975. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 10858, Electric Utility Regulatory Reform Act. (Box 7)
      - H.R. 11991, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of, Amended., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15141, Elementary and Secondary Education Act of, Amended, re Health Professions., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.Con.Res. 354, Elimination of Illegal Drug Traffic from Turkey. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 516, Allen J. Ellender Fellowship. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8588, Emergency Employment Countercyclical Assistance Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4462, Emergency Jobs and Unemployment Assistance Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9246, Emergency Medical Services Systems Act Amendments of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 17688, H.J.Res. 387, H.Res. 604, Emergency Petroleum Allocation Act of, Amended (3)., 1973 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5870, Emergency Petroleum Allocation Act of, Enforcement., 1973 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4464, Emergency Unemployment Compensation Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4683, Emergency Unemployment Health Benefits Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7813, Employee Retirement Income Security Act of, Amended., 1974 (Box 8)
      - H.Res. 387, Energy Administration, re Overcome Energy Shortage. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9176, Energy Industry Deconcentration Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8243, Energy Information Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6415, Energy-Materials Conservation Education Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9218, Environmental Health Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8488, H.R. 10819, Equal Opportunity for Displaced Homemakers Act (2). (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7040, Establish an Office of Food Administration. (Box 8)
      - H.Res. 620, Establish a Permanent Select Committee on Energy. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6744, Executive Agreements Review Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 17642, Extend Entitlement of Veterans to Educational Assistance from 36 to 45 Months. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7530, Fair Marketing of Petroleum Products Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4150, Fair Packaging and Labeling Act, Amended. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7248, Farmer's Market Bill. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8881, Farm Tax Equity Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12015, H.R. 12406, Federal Election Campaign Act Amendments of (2)., 1976 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6271, Federal Employees Gift Disclosure Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8838, Federal Employees' Political Activities Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.Con.Res. 290, Federal Income Tax Forms. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5300, Federal Protective Service Within General Services Administration. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 10960, Federal Taxpayer's Rights Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7485, Federal Utility and Energy Low-Income Subsidy Act of, 1974. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7060, Federal Water Pollution Control Act, Amended. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5672, Firearm Control Act, re 5 Year Prison Term. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 493, Fishermen's Protective Act of, Amended., 1967 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6350, Flexible Hours Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 2396, Food Allowance for Older Americans Act of, 1973. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 2577, H.R. 2412, H.R. 2415, H.R. 7518, Food Stamp Act of, Amended (4)., 1964 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12442, Food Stamp Act of, Rules and Regulation Changes., 1964 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15749, Foreclosure Forbearance Standards Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6997, Foreign Military Sales Act, Amended. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12255, Foreign Paramilitary Intervention Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9151, Foreign Service Act, Amended. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9241, Franchising Practices Reform Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4339, Freedom from Military Surveillance Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6010, Freedom of Information Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4319, General Accounting Office Authorization to Audit Federal Reserve Board. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12208, Government Economy and Spending Reform Act of, 1976. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6026, Government in the Sunshine Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9128, Grain Export Control Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4604, Grand Jury Reform Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15143, Grants for Disadvantaged Background Persons for Schooling in Dentistry. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6158, Ground Propulsion Systems Research and Development Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7070, Handgun Crime Control Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 21, Health Security Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4221, Higher Education Act of, Amended, re Work-Study Funds., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 14070, Higher Education Act of, Amended., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15142, Higher Education Act of, Amended, re Grants for Disadvantaged Students for Medical School., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12851, Higher Education Amendments of, 1976. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4302, Home Health Services Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5842, Home Improvement Incentive Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6113, Housing Act of, Amended., 1937 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6502, Housing Act of, Amended and Extended., 1964 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6080, Illegal Campaign Contributions. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4595, H.R. 5661, Impoundment Control Act of, Amended (2)., 1974 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7598, H.R. 8494, H.R. 6936, Industrial Energy Conservation Act of (3)., 1975 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 13782, Inflation Against Consumers. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 8943, Interfuel Competition Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15828, Intelligence Management Reform Act of, 1976. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7449, Intergovernmental Countercyclical Assistance Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 14631, H.R. 11236, H.R. 10607, H.R. 10907, Internal Revenue Code of, Amended (4)., 1954 (Box 8)
      - Internal Revenue Code, Amended
        - H.R. 4135, re Tax on Cigarettes. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 9003, re National Cancer Institute Research. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 2066, re Thermal Design. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 4640, re Transportation to Employment. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 4669, re Unemployment Extended to Agricultural Workers. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 7256, re Nursing Home Expenses H.Con.Res. 302, International Women's Year. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 7092, H.R. 8855, Interns for Political Leadership Act of (2)., 1975 (Box 8)
        - H.R. 14668, Lands for D-Q University. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 5143, Legislative Reorganization Act of, Amended., 1970 (Box 8)
        - H.R. 11233, Library Services and Construction Act, Amended. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 11491, H.R. 12180, Lifeline Rate Act of (2)., 1976 (Box 8)
        - H.R. 5198, Limit Internal Revenue on Tax Inspection. (Box 8)
        - H.R. 4867, H.R. 5882, Limousine Limitation Act of (2)., 1975 (Box 8)
        - H.R. 9256, Lobbying Equalization Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
        - H.Res. 487, H.Res. 575, Malnutrition in Certain Areas of the World (2). (Box 8)
        - H.R. 12425, Marijuana Control Act of, 1976. (Box 8)
      - H.Con.Res. 98, Martin Luther King, Jr. Bronze Bust or Statue. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 1810, Martin Luther King, Jr. Legal Holiday. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5306, Military Discharge Bill. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 14822, Maternal and Child Health Care Act. (Box 8)
      - H.Res. 981, Praising Work of Clarence Mitchell, Jr. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5833, Magnetohydrodynamics (MHD) Research, Development and Demonstration Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 2206, The Mexican-American Rural Community Anti-Poverty Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7251, H.R. 7446, Mortgage Disclosure Act of (2)., 1975 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5041, Motion Picture Industry to Pay Prevailing Wages Regarding Contracts. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4679, Mutual Security Act of, Amended., 1954 (Box 8)
      - H.Res. 1228, Name Two Mountains in Alaska After Late Congressmen Boggs and Begich. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4901, National Adoption Information Exchange System. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 472, National Autistic Children's Week. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 1011, National Bicentennial Day of Prayer of Thanksgiving and Guidance. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6457, National Cancer Institute. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4355, National Center for the Prevention and Control of Rape. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 11111, National Climate Program Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12747, National Commission on Food Production, etc. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 956, H.J.Res. 1054, National Community Health Week (2). (Box 8)
      - H.R. 3763, National Condominium Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 4355, National Center for the Prevention and Control of Rape. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 2241, National Conservation Area of the California Desert. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 10881, H.R. 14513, National Consumer Cooperative Bank Act (2). (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 281, National Day of Remembrance of Man's Inhumanity to Man. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 5928, National Electrical Energy Conservation Act. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 833, National Employ the Older Worker Week. (Box 8)
      - H.J.Res. 305, H.J.Res. 877, National Food Day (2). (Box 8)
      - H.R. 12355, National Forest Timber Management Reform Act of, 1976. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7782, National Foundation on the Arts and Humanities Act of, Amended., 1965 (Box 8)
      - H.R. 3750, National Energy and Conservation Corporation (AMPOWER). (Box 8)
      - H.R. 13598, National Housing Act, Amended, re HUD Dwellings. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 7349, National Labor Relations Act, Amended. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 13221, National Museum of Afro-American History and Culture at Wilberforce. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 15457, National Neighborhood Policy Act. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 9242, National Nutrition Education Act of, 1975. (Box 8)
      - H.R. 6011, National Oil Recycling Act. (Box 8)